(BOTH GREETlNG lN SPANlSH)
(PHONE RlNGlNG)
Hello, Dunder Mifflin.
No, no, no. No.
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
l believe that every
man, woman, and child
in this country
should learn how
to speak Spanish.
They are our neighbors
to the south, and this
would be a healing thing
for all of North America.
And l am going
on vacation next
week to Cancún.
(GREETlNG lN SPANlSH)
(CHATTERlNG lN SPANlSH)
(LAUGHS UNCOMFORTABLY)
(GREETlNG lN SPANlSH)
(GREETlNG lN GERMAN)
l don't understand
why Michael is wasting
his time with Spanish.
l have it on very
good authority that
within 20 years,
everyone will be
speaking German.
Or a Chinese-German hybrid.
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH lNCORRECTLY)
(CORRECTlNG lN SPANlSH)
Michael's having
a hard time with the
gender part of Spanish.
So, l told him
to mark everything
with the international
symbol for gender.
And. . .
l should have been
more specific.
Your office is full
of genitalia.
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
"That's what he says"?
Damn it.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
Ah, Angelo!
Angela.
Michael.
(SPEAKlNG SPANlSH)
(SCOFFS)
All right, so l'll finish up
on bulk pricing and then you
go into delivery guarantees.
You know, maybe
there's an opportunity
for a joke there, like. . .
Like, "l just
delivered a baby.
"They didn't offer
me a guarantee."
Yeah. Maybe we don't
even need that.
Can you smell the power?
Halperts, power couple.
You know what?
l should be getting
this client, Michael.
My numbers are better
than either of theirs.
l went with the people
l thought would put the
best face on the company.
lf you want people
to put the best face
on something,
why would you
get two people
who probably have
never cut the face off
of anything in their lives?
lt's a good point.
This is our first
joint sales pitch.
l think we're gonna work
really well together.
Yeah. l think we have
complementary strengths.
We understand
each other.
We have good
give and take.
l give, he takes!
l don't even know
who you are anymore.
(EXCLAlMS)
Hi. Donna Newton.
Here to see Michael Scott.
Hey, Miss Newton. Hi.
l'm Jim. How are you?
Did somebody order
a hooker over here?
Stop that. Hi.
Hi. How are you?
There's this woman
l met a few weeks ago.
Her name is Donna.
Manager of a Sid
and Dexter's.
And right now,
we're in the midst of
a passionate love affair.
No, but she is coming
by today, maybe to buy
some printers, so. . .
Right here, we have
the wonder twins,
Jim and Pam Halpert.
They will be
assisting you today.
You look exactly alike.
No, we're
actually married.
We're not
brother and sister.
l have a sense
about these things.
All right.
You have some ancestors
in common somewhere back.
l knew it.
You should see
their baby.
So, yes, laser printers
are more expensive, but
they cost less to operate,
so it's a trade-off.
(KNOCKlNG AT DOOR)
Hi. Sorry to interrupt.
Little time sensitive.
Do you, Donna,
by any chance
shop at Victoria's Secret?
What?
Because l keep
getting these magazines
sent to me
via the address of the woman
who used to live in my condo
before me.
None of this
is time sensitive.
Yes, the sale's on
now through May.
Oh, yeah, thank you.
Okay. l have more of them.
You would have weekly
conference calls with
executives in corporate,
a two week training
program at the Yale
School of Management.
Obviously you would be
high on the list for
advancement opportunities.
Sounds all right.
What is this?
This is Print
ln All Colors,
Sabre's minority
executive training program.
(SCOFFS) lt doesn't
just sound "aite,"
it sounds amazing.
l didn't say "aite."
How do l apply?
You have to be a minority.
Glasses wearers,
cholera survivors,
You want me to keep going?
Those don't really count.
We're thinking more ethnic
and racial minorities.
Come here. Come here.
Ten seconds ago
this guy was driving
a forklift, okay?
Now, all of a sudden,
he's Cinderella of the office?
What are you guys thinking?
l like the sound of this.
Maybe one day
l'll be sitting
in Michael's chair.
Wouldn't that be something?
DWlGHT: One minority
from this branch is going
to get into this program.
Who would l prefer? Hmm.
The competent hardworking one
who does things his own way,
or the malleable simpleton
who can be bought for
a few fashion magazines?
This is the second time
that you've sent me
the wrong size.
l mean, l know what
a four should feel like.
l've been a four
my whole life.
You know what?
You can go to hell, all right?
Thanks for nothing.
Oh, man.
White people, right?
l don't know
if she was white.
Well, you can kind of
tell from their voice.
Yeah.
l bet you get pulled over
by the cops a lot just
because of your race.
Well, they say
it's because of texting,
but maybe you're right.
l think you should consider
applying for the executive
minority training program.
l never thought of myself
as an executive before.
l know, 'cause you
have no role models.
How many lndian CEOs
can you think of?
l can't think of
any CEOs, any race.
You could be
the lndian Bill Gates.
the lndian Ted Turner.
l could be
the lndian Julia Roberts.
That's not. . . She's. . .
Okay. Yes.
l took the liberty to scan
a few things earlier,
and l want to show you. . .
There we go!
Look at those vivid colors.
Look at my eyes.
Those are
Shrek-green eyes.
That is me again.
l think this displays
the crisp, dazzling white.
And that would
be a display
of the crisp,
gorgeous black.
DONNA: Yeah.
lt's subtle.
lt's how it works.
I show her an image
that turns her on,
and then she looks at me,
then she looks at the image,
then back at me,
then back at the image.
Soon she doesn't
know what is me,
what is the image,
she just knows
that she's turned on.
This is a place that
l like to go to be
alone with my thoughts.
l've never taken
anybody there before.
Who took the photo?
Ryan.
Oh.
And that's it.
That's me.
That's who l am.
Not bad.
Oh, thanks.
You're not bad, either.
Thank you.
(CLEARlNG THROAT)
Oh, my God.
Jim, could you come
in here for a sec?
What was that printer
we were looking at?
You didn't see it, Pam.
She was giving me all
sorts of signals that she
wanted me to make a move.
Shortbread?
No.
l'll have one.
Well, maybe
you shouldn't try
to kiss people at work.
Oh, really, Jim?
What about Pam?
And you did a heck
of a lot more than kiss.
Maybe this could
be my Pam.
Okay, well,
all that is irrelevant. . .
Maybe Michael
has a point.
l mean,
if she was really that upset,
she wouldn't still be here.
Was it professional? No.
But l work
in the nightlife industry.
l get hit on all the time.
ln my 20s,
it would've been annoying.
ln my late 20s,
l find it really flattering.
Look, l know that
l screwed up in there.
l know that l probably
messed up your sale.
l just want to go
in and fix it.
What if l back out
and you finish
the pitch with Jim?
What?
What was that?
Just let him flirt with her.
People meet each
other all sorts of ways.
Pam, you know he's not
gonna get anywhere and
he's gonna blow our sale.
Who cares?
lt's not that huge a sale.
Hey, the Schwab guy
told us to treat every sale
like it was a huge sale.
Don't act like you understood
anything that guy said.
Good luck, wingman.
How has being
a minority affected you?
Well, there's
a lot of pressure
from my parents
to settle down
and marry an lndian guy.
Oh, good. And you
resent this because. . .
lndian guys always wear
their cell phones outside
their pants. lt's so dorky.
No, no, no. That's not dorky.
Look, it's easily accessible.
Boom. Like this.
91 1 , hello.
Scranton Strangler's
in the house.
lnside the house!
Just put it
in your pocket.
(CHATTERlNG)
Look at that.
She's totally
flirting with him.
You don't know that.
Some people can't
help oozing sexuality.
You ever notice
you can only ooze
two things?
Sexuality and pus.
Man, l tell you.
She just crossed
her arms together.
That's bad.
Maybe she's just pushing
her breasts together
to make them look bigger.
Like that?
ls this the best
you can do right now?
For that printer, yes.
Unfortunately
we don't have
a lot of flexibility.
Oh. Well, l guess
l'm just used to the
restaurant business where,
if you're in charge
then you can always
get discounts
for the people
that you like.
JlM: Yeah.
Maybe we can find
a little wiggle room, right?
What's that?
Maybe we can find
some wiggle room.
(SlGHlNG)
l don't. . .
l don't think so.
l think we could.
l don't see how we could
possibly sell these for that
little without losing money.
Delivery alone will cost. . .
Okay, well, sometimes,
sometimes it makes financial
sense to lose money, right?
Like, for tax purposes.
Actually, l ran
the numbers on this,
and in this case,
it makes more financial
sense to gain money.
Why don't you
run them again?
What if she's just
flirting with you
to get a better price?
lf she is,
it's working.
Yeah, Michael, here's a trick.
Ask her if she wants a mint.
lf she says no,
then she is not
interested.
She does not like him.
You can flirt with someone
to get what you want and
also be attracted to them.
How do you think
we got together?
'Cause l stopped
by your desk, like,
1 5 times a day.
l was after your money.
Well, the joke was on you.
Yes, it was.
Can you stop
micromanaging?
l know how to do this.
You're yelling. . .
Okay. Okay.
What are you guys doing?
This girl was really rude
to me at the mall,
so l created a fake lM
account from a hot guy
at her high school,
and now l'm trying
to make her anorexic.
Tell her everyone
in homeroom
thinks she's fat.
KELLY: That is so good.
You know, we really
should keep practicing
for this interview.
Oh, that's okay.
Ryan coached me.
Ryan? What does he know?
lt's easy. You just
turn every question
around on them.
Do you think you're
treated differently
because of your race?
Would you ask
that same question
if l was white?
We're so in.
We?
When l become executive,
l'm gonna make Ryan manager.
And then the two of us
are cleaning house.
DWIGHT: Kelly will be
even worse than Darryl.
lf you'd have told
me this morning
that today l'd be creating
a monster capable
of my own destruction,
l'd have thought you were
referring to the bull Mose
and l are trying to reanimate.
"So, corporate approval
of this contract is contingent
upon buyer and seller
"obtaining. . ."
Blah-de-blah-de-blah.
"Boilerplate,
pound of fish."
Just kidding.
Do you like mints?
Yes.
l carry mints
with me sometimes.
Oh, l haven't
tried those.
Ever tried those?
No.
They're good.
You want one?
Sure.
lt's like. . .
"Cool. . . Certified cool."
l like how they
say "certified."
Like there's some
consortium of. . .
Michael !
l'm sorry.
l can't stop myself
from kissing her.
Yeah. Now you know
how l feel sitting next
to those M&M's all day.
Well, why don't you
just move the M&M's?
Why don't you shut up?
Okay. Guys, guys, guys,
just tell me it's not totally
insane to try one more time.
lt is totally insane.
Michael, he's right.
You are turning
into a stalker.
(SlGHlNG) Okay.
What do you think?
l think it's over, man.
Andy?
(GROANlNG)
Okay, some for,
some against.
Nobody's for.
Pam.
Hmm?
What do you think?
l think it's really,
really unlikely.
Okay.
Really unlikely.
But l can't say
that it's impossible.
What?
l'm not saying
she's in love with him,
but she could have
left a while ago.
Most printer sales
are done over the phone,
Miss Boob Shirt.
l'm going
with Pam's group.
Wait. Michael.
Okay.
Michael. Michael.
No. Guys, guys, guys, guys,
just thank you for talking.
Wish me luck.
JlM: No.
What sort of movie
would Rudy have been
if he had just stopped
and given up
after two rejections?
Would have been a lot shorter,
probably been a lot funnier,
but it would have
ultimately been
a disappointment.
l still would have seen it,
but that's not the point.
Kelly is disqualified.
What?
You said the program
is not open to Caucasians.
Well, anthropologically,
she is lndian.
lndians migrated
from the Caucasus
region of Europe.
Therefore, technically,
she is Caucasian.
You're welcome, America.
Yeah, but she's
not white, though.
Well, obviously
she's brownish,
but come on.
l mean, Darryl is
far more ethnic.
Darryl withdrew
his application.
The dates of the Yale program
interfered with his softball
league, so he's gone.
l got my whole life
to be a minority executive.
l only have about
a year left in
these knees, though.
So Kelly is
the only applicant.
Yeah, unless somebody
else applies today.
(GREETlNG lN HlNDl)
Oh, dear God. Okay.
Don't make any
decisions just yet. Okay?
l'll be right back.
Hello.
That's very nice.
l never noticed
that before.
Sometimes my bangs cover it.
Yeah. l don't want
to be offensive, but may
l ask you what that means?
l do find that offensive,
actually.
We should have
your contract done
by Thursday.
Oh, great! Great.
l will look out
for that stuff, then.
Okay.
And. . .
You know, l just wanted to say
it was really, really nice
to do business with you.
Yeah. lt was nice
to do business
with you, too.
Thank you.
Did l get everything?
l don't know.
l think so.
Yeah, l think so.
Okay.
So. . . Oh ! Donna?
DONNA: Yeah.
Do you need validation?
We don't validate.
No. lt's just
in the lot, so. . .
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
Mmm.
Bye.
(CLEARlNG THROAT)
So, if you have. . .
lf there's any
other questions
that you have. . .
l don't have any
other questions.
l'm just gonna make
my way down to. . .
MlCHAEL: Okay.
All right. Bye.
DONNA: Bye-bye.
Have a good elevator ride.
DONNA: Okay.
What's that out there?
Michael,
how did it go?
How would one of you feel
if l told you l could
put you on a fast track
to an executive position
at this company?
Holy cow.
l'd be so happy.
l wasn't talking to you,
pale face.
l know. l meant
l'd be happy for them.
What l'm offering is a ticket
on a bullet train straight
to middle management.
Dwight, l know
these programs.
Every color is important,
because together
we make a rainbow.
Yes.
l'll slap you in the
face with a rainbow.
Mmm.
Speaking of rainbows,
Oscar, you are kind
of a double minority.
Gay.
So, we at Sabre
could really benefit
from your perspective.
Dwight, we know
Kelly applied.
We're not going to cross her,
no matter how good
the program is.
l can protect
you from Kelly.
(SCOFFS)
Will you get out
of here? Seriously.
For hobbies, yoga,
belly dancing,
snake-charming,
beds of nails,
l like lying. . .
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
This is Hidetosha Hacigawa.
He would like to apply
for the Sabre Minority
Executive Training Program,
Print ln All
Colors initiative.
Dwight, what
are you doing?
Helping heal America
in a dramatic fashion
in the eleventh hour.
God, l hate you so much.
Caucasians.
Am l right?
Have a seat.
l'll translate.
Why? l don't
need translator. . .
You don't know
what you need, just. . .
Why don't you tell me
a little about yourself, Hide.
(SPEAKlNG ENGLlSH)
(SlGHlNG)
Hey, Michael,
how you doing?
l don't know.
Can't really trust
my feelings anymore.
You know what, Michael?
For what it's worth,
l was wrong, too.
l thought she was
interested in you.
She suckered you, too?
Was it the cleavage?
Yeah, and the
shoulder cutouts.
Yep.
Michael, you know,
it's easy to get fooled.
Bob's warehouse guys
flirt with me all the time.
lt's mostly harmless.
Usually l don't
let it go too far.
You know, when
l tore my scrote,
l was. . .
l was seeing this really
hot urologist about it
and thought she was into me,
but now l think she
was just doing a bunch
of stuff to bill my HMO.
You know,
she's touching
around down there.
lt's easy to
get confused.
Michael, l think
Donna left this here.
Should l put it in
the lost and found for 1 4 days
and then l can take it home?
God.
She left this here? Okay.
Maybe she wants me
to return this
to her at her work.
What? No.
No.
KEVlN: No.
Yeah. This could
be a signal.
People don't just
take barrettes off.
lt's not a signal.
lt's just a coincidence.
No, it's not even
a coincidence.
lt's just something
that happened.
Michael.
Well. . .
She doesn't want you
to return the barrette.
She's not interested in you.
l know. l know. l know.
l'm sorry.
l know. You're right.
Thank you.
Thanks, everybody.
(CLEARlNG THROAT)
No.
Michael !
(SlGHlNG)
Oh, you're still here.
l have your baguette.
Everyone, it is my
pleasure to announce
our newest member
of the Sabre Minority
Executive Training Program,
Kelly Rajanigandha Kapoor.
They're going to be
pretty pleased
in Tallahassee
that l snagged
an lndian for the program.
She'll be the first.
The program's mostly black.
lt's almost too black.
That didn't sound right.
And the best part is,
is that l get a business
stipend
to buy all new clothes.
KEVlN: Awesome.
So you can totally buy
any of my old clothes
that l'm not gonna
need anymore.
Oh, my God,
thank you so much.
l love that denim
jumpsuit you have.
How much?
Actually, l was thinking about
clothes that l was just going
to give to Goodwill anyway.
Great.
Hey, kiddo.
Congratulations are in order.
You deserve it.
Thank you, Dwight.
Oh.
l'll never forget everything
that you've done for me.
Gosh. (LAUGHS)
Because l never
forget anything.
Just once l would like
to be a puppet master
and have nothing go wrong.
ls that too much to ask?
You know what? Everybody
told me that you weren't
interested. Everybody.
And l didn't believe them.
And they were right.
So, here's your barrette.
No, you were right.
Who?
You were right.
About what?
l'm sorry.
No. No. No.
l'm. . .
Nope.
What happened?
Kelly got into
the minority
training program.
Really? Oh, that's great.
That's such good news.
l did it.
l kissed. We kissed.
Oh, Michael. . .
No, l'm serious.
The. . . This happened.
l went down to
the parking lot and l was. . .
l returned her barrette.
We. . .
We did. Okay.
We did. We did.
You know what?
lt doesn't matter,
because l know what happened,
and that is all that counts.
l did do it!